[Music]
it's quite normal for me to spend a day
by myself where i don't encounter
another person
i want to share a little insight into
that day with you and at the end of this
video let's have a sit down chat so stay
tuned
and we'll talk some more
[Music]
so
wax currants are not a popular berries
since they barely have any flavor but
they have very high pectin content and
so it's quite easy to mix them with
another berry
and make jams or jellies and preserves
i was once told that native american
peoples
would eat these berries as a source of
nutrition in times of hardship but
i can't be sure that that is true
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
i have only a handful of highly
meaningful relationships in my life and
it is by choice
and i do spend a lot of time alone
my hobbies include
painting and reading and
puttering about outdoors and so
i can easily go an entire day without
seeing another human
i do have a very loving and supportive
family and partner who i regularly spend
time with
but i always make sure
to
keep time for myself and to listen to my
spirit and
what my introverted needs are
i also have a menagerie of pets with
quite obnoxious personalities that keep
me highly entertained
from the perspective of many people i
live quite an isolated lifestyle which
is so interesting
to me to think about since
i feel like i live a life of such
abundance and isolation is often
connected to a scarcity
but it is true i i do live in a very
rural area and i travel much less than i
ever have before
yet i do find myself extremely happy
probably the happiest i've been since i
was a child now i don't wish to sell
this lifestyle as an ideal i i
definitely don't think it is appropriate
for every spirit
i don't believe there's one lifestyle or
even belief system that applies to
everyone coming to live here was not
easy at first um i had to rewrite the
thesis of my entire life in order to be
happy here
and it was a challenge that i'm so
thankful i persevered through
i had to let go of what i perceived to
be success
i was a very competitive university
student
and i was
addicted to the pursuit of wealth and
i connected wealth to freedom to live
how i wanted and the irony of it
was that neither was i making much money
even though i was working hard
but
i was also not living my dream and
consequently i was constantly living in
the future
day-to-day life felt like a strange
meaningless cycle in which there was no
end after moving here it took quite a
long time to pull myself out of the haze
and to
really open my eyes
and appreciate the wonder and beauty
of where i lived it was a process of
coming home to my inner spirit and
i'm so happy now to say that i can more
easily relate to my five-year-old self
than my 19 year old self and
in my personal story that's a very good
thing
all this being said i'm just sitting
here telling you a
tiny part of my individual story
i hope that through these videos i might
be able to contribute a little bit of
insight into another lifestyle and
another pace of living that may align
with yours
or inspire you
if anything i want to share my passion
for
growing a sense of abundance
through simple living i have found my
truth by
learning how to silence my mind and
listen to my inner spirit
it's an ongoing process and i am no
master of it but i keep trying and
i think that's all we need to expect of
ourselves to do
i hope that today you might be inspired
to take a moment and to
go into the quiet and to
listen to your soul and ask it what it
needs
and also ask
the people in your life what they need
and learn how to find a balance between
sharing and loving and
loving yourself
subscribe if you want to see videos
every wednesday um in the meantime have
a wonderful day
hugs and kisses to everyone
bye